

JOHN PHILIP MATUNOG FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER/VA

Born: August 22, 1990

General Santos City, Philippines

Mobile:+639104348571 Skype Id: jaypeebm22

https://philvergriffin.github.io



ABOUT

Hi! I'm John Philip Matunog, a freelance web designer and front-end web developer. I first had interest in web development after I attended a seminar in web development held at Davao City, Philippines 3 years ago. After that, my brother encouraged me to hone my skills in web development through self study and freelance jobs. Before I became a Web Developer, I also had experience working as a Virtual Assistant for a year and a half. My goal as an online freelancer is to become an all in one package type of employee to fulfill the needs of my employer.

OBJECTIVES

I am a very keen worker which requires minimum supervision and very trustworthy. My objective is to complement your needs and goals with the quality of my work, therefore contributing to your company's success.

EDUCATION

HOLY TRINITY COLLEGE – **GSC** (June2011) Bachelor of Science in Secondary Education

ALABEL NATIONAL HIGH SCHOOL (March2006)
Senior's President, SSG President
Sports Writer – School Publication

EXPERIENCES

Web Developer - Freelance (February2014-Present) Various Clients

VA/Social Media Account Manager (January2012-July2013) Tom Johns (*Early Buckets*)

Sales Representative (June2009 – December2010) Robinson's Department Store General Santos City, Philippines

TECHNICAL EXPERTISE

HTML5 CSS3 PHP **jQuery Javascript** Wordpress Bootstrap PSD to HTML **UI** Design Typography Responsive Web Design Web Standards Website Optimization Logo Design Infusionsoft Virtual Assistant Services



